{
    "subject": "resource/Demob_(TV_series)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:British_comedy-drama_television_programmes",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Demob (TV series) is British comedy-drama television programmes.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.747338056564331,
            "question": "Is Demob a British production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7292019128799438,
            "question": "What genre is the TV series Demob?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6865410804748535,
            "question": "Is there a dramatic element to the storyline of Demob?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5753165483474731,
            "question": "What is the primary focus of the TV series Demob?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5729550123214722,
            "question": "What elements might contribute to the comedic aspect of Demob?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5517725944519043,
            "question": "Does Demob fall under the comedy genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5437802076339722,
            "question": "What type of program is Demob classified as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43121883273124695,
            "question": "Who are the likely target viewers for Demob?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3825576603412628,
            "question": "Can you describe the style of programming used in Demob?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3064623773097992,
            "question": "What is the intended tone or mood of Demob?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Demob (TV series) is British comedy-drama television programmes.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3360_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the style of programming used in Demob?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3360_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the likely target viewers for Demob?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3360_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of program is Demob classified as?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3360_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3360_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3360_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3360_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3360_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3360_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3360_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3360_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3360_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3360_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3360_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provided describe Demob as a \"short-lived British comedy-drama television series\", which matches the subject of interest. Therefore, based on this information, it can be confirmed that the statement about Demob being a British comedy-drama television programme is correct."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that \"Demob\" is a British comedy-drama television series, with details such as its broadcast on ITV in 1993 and the format of being a six-episode series."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}